[id: iauvwwqz]
[ar:Michael Jackson]
[ti:Bad]
[00:00]Michael Jackson - Bad
[00:18]Your butt is mine
[00:20]gonna tell you right
[00:22]Just show your face in broad daylight.
[00:26]I'm telling you on how I feel

[00:30]Gonna hurt your mind
[00:33]don't shoot to kill
[00:34]Come on
[00:36]come on
[00:37]lay it on me
[00:38]all right.
[00:43]I'm giving you on count of three
[00:47]To show your stuff or let it be.
[00:51]I'm telling you
[00:54]just watch your mouth
[00:55]I know your game
[00:58]what you're about.
[01:00][01:59]they say the sky's the limit
[01:02][02:01]and to me that's really true
[01:04][02:03]my friend
[01:05][02:04]you have seen nothing
[01:06][02:05]just wait 'til I get through -

[01:08][02:07][02:57]Because I'm bad
[01:09][01:18][02:08][02:17][02:59][03:07][03:16]I'm bad - come on
[01:12][01:16][02:11][02:15][03:02][03:06][03:15][03:18][03:23][03:36][03:48][03:52][03:57]You know I'm bad
[01:14][02:13][03:03][03:20]I'm bad - you know it!
[01:21][02:20][03:10][03:27][03:44][04:02]And the whole world has to answer right now
[01:23][02:22][03:13][03:29]Just to tell you once again who's bad!
[01:26][02:24]
[01:34]The word is out
[01:36]you're doin' wrong
[01:38]Gonna lock you up before too long.
[01:42]your lyin' eyes gonna tell you right
[01:45]So listen up
[01:48]don't make a fight!
[01:50]Your talk is cheap
[01:53]you're not a man
[01:55]Wou're throwin' stones to hide your hands.

[02:50]We can change the world tomorrow
[02:52]this could be a better place
[02:54]If you don't like what I'm sayin'
[02:56]then won't you slap my face -




[03:32]You know I'm smooth
[03:33][03:50][03:58]I'm bad - you know it
[03:37]I'm bad
[03:40]You know
[03:42]you know it - come on

[03:46]Just to tell you once again.

[03:54]I'm bad - you know!
[04:01]you know
[04:03]Just to tell you once again. Who's bad?

